Notes from meeting with professor Sahoo:


In mood paper: mood and anxiety data were collected on a daily basis. Paper looks at data in weekly windows for 12 weeks. Each window has mood and anxiety data. We take the mean and stdDev for each window.

If there is 4 responses per weekly window we can use the data. If there are less then 4 days of data we don’t use the data. 

￼

We want to parse the csv file, and randomly remove a day from their dataset. And recalculate the features, do the same for 2 days removed.

moodmean, moodSTDV, anxietymean, anxietySTDV

